Hello everyone！
I'm KoFan with cuteness , innocence,
beauty , elegance , vigor, cheerness, youth and talent ,
with angel face, devil body, and kindness.
Everyone knows I like Harry Potter so much
That Here we call the Meow House Shop,maybe.
There are a lot of series of co-branded uniforms with Harry Potter.
Although I think its uniform is not an orthodox uniform
Its shirt is a bit like made of cotton
And the skirt is not very orthodox
But I still think it's pretty cute
Then there happened to be another one in Taiwan
A Photo studio of Magician's Chamber
I think it's super cute
I made a special appointment one day and went to take a photograph.
You can appreciate the photos later
Um…
Actually this is my first time
To take a photograph so seriously
Because I really like harry potter
Also I like this series of clothes
And a series about magic
I'm really worried that I can't shoot well
I hope after everyone appreciate
You can give me some criticism and advice of the photos
Before the video starts
I want to tell everyone
Because its material is made by cotton
And
Although I have ironed and cleaned up cat hair.
Because I have three cats
It still has some wrinkled feeling or
Not good enough
Please forgive me and hope everyone can be considerate
I'm sorry about that
At the beginning
First of all we have to say
Everyone can take a look at my costume
I'm from HufflePuff College
In the beginning
Because of the movie,
everyone might have been more likely
in Gryffindor or Slytherin.
At first, I thought I should be in Gryffindor
because
When I was young,I felt that Gryffindor was the best
And Slytherin was the worst
But in the end I felt that I should be
Hufflepuff
Because I am not as smart as Ravenclaw
Nor as courageous as Gryffindor
Nor as ambitious as Slytherin
So
I think at least my only strength is kindness
Can I say that?
I don’t think people can be 100% of kind
But I think I should be regarded as a kind-hearted
Witch
Let's take a look at the first set
HufflePuff
The first set, the representative yellow of HufflePuff
I bought this cloak at Universal Studios Japan
I think that it is
Cute
All right
Everyone can look at the bow tie
It's a complete set
And there is the school badge on the chest
There is also a copper badge inside the skirt
And in behind,
there is the sailor collar of HufflePuff
This one is blue
I think it is kind of academic style
It is because Ravenclaw
that
I made a very smart feeling.
The feeling of holding a pile of books
I don’t think they made the bow
Very orthodox
But I really like this place around the waist
Look at here.
Each piece has a different color in each college
do you know?
When the Sorting Hat was assigning Hermione Jean Granger,
it is hesitating whether she should go to Ravenclaw.
Because she is so smart
It should be said that it is just a personality trait
Maybe there is a person who actually has 4 talents
4 ability
Maybe he has it
Finally
It’s a very popular Gryffindor
I tied a ponytail
Looks more vitality
Be vigorous
Then please ignore the hem of my dress
I seem to forget to make it swing
And I don’t know where did I put the bow tie
So I matched a tie by myself
But I think it shouldn’t be matched look so bad
Then this scene
I'm learning from Hermione Jean Granger
The scene when she was making the Polyjuice Potion before
Although my appearance is not as good as
Hermione Jean Granger
but
when I'm imitating my idol
I still feel pretty happy
Antlers! I wanted to test everyone, which character was called Antlers？
At last
I want to apologize to everyone
Sorry.
I don't have Slytherin uniform
As I said, I was a person who sees things be black and white
black-and-white thinking
This is my personality
but
I reread the novel a few times after I grow up
Although sometimes in my childhood ...
Ahh...that's another story.
When I was young, my family had a strict discipline.
I was kept from computers, mobile phones,
TVs or something like that.
So I read the Harry Potter novels all day
From episode 1 to ...  how many episodes have been published at that time?  Episode 5?
I read it from episode 1 to 5.
and I started another round from episode 1 to 5
Then another round.  Again and again.
I used to take a flashlight and read stories of Harry Potter in the quilt.
I felt that I am doing the same thing
Like Harry Potter hides in the quilt and
reads the magic books during the holidays.
Oh, wait ! I have to apologize to everyone.
I don't have clothes of Slytherin
But when I grew up, I realized that
we aren't black and white in a world.
It's just like
Severus Snape belongs to
Slytherin's
Do you think he is a bad guy？
Is he really a bad guy?
Is he really harmful？
Had he indeed directly kill anyone?
I think
what he had done actually is that he wanted to integrate with everyone
integrate with everyone.
He doesn't have his
Own social circle
So
He will
want to take refuge in
the power of Lord Voldemort,
because he wants to make himself stronger.
However I think his innate character is good
Are the people in the Gryffindor really good forever?
You can see that Luna Lovegood had been bullied with her things hidden.
And even
Harry Potter's Dad, James Potter
Although both they were fighting
and playing tricks on each other,
Those actions are still some kind of bullying.
So, I started to think about that. Really? Is it like this?
In the end I discovered that all the four houses have their own pros and cons.
It doesn't mean that
Only the dark wizard is assigned to Slytherin
Because I recently made this video,
Without Slytherin's uniform.
I think it's a pity .
So
I search the internet about Slytherin's uniform,
As I mentioned earlier about the meow shop.
It sold the series of co-branded with Harry Potter again
So
I immediately bought Slytherin's uniform
But it may not be seen in this video,
I'm so sorry about that
I hope this video could
???
Could make you happy when you watch this video
I really like Harry Potter very much
If everyone who likes Harry Potter,
The wizards
want to see me share more about that
I've been to Universal Studios in Japan before.
I went to New York to see that
The Musical of the Cursed Child,
and I bought some accessories,
If you want to see
I hope that you could support me
So
see you next time
nox
I recommend a YouTuber who was Frog Knife Saint
He did a very detailed analysis of Harry Potter
If you are interested, you can visit his channel