Hello everyone！
I'm KoFan！who is cute and innocent
Beautiful temperament, elegant, energetic, cheerful, young and talented
Have a pretty child-like face but a charming full-grown and figure kind-hearted ！
Everyone knows I like Harry Potter so much
That should be called Meow House Shop
He has co-branded with Harry Potter to produce a series of uniforms
Although I think it's uniform is not an orthodox uniform
His shirt is a bit like made of cotton
And the skirt is not very orthodox
But I still think it's pretty cute
Then there happened to be another one in Taiwan
A Photo studio of Magician's Chamber
I think it's super cute
I made a special appointment for a day and went to take a photograph
You can appreciate the photos later
Um…
Actually this is my first time
To take a photograph so seriously
Because I really like harry potter
Also I like this series of clothes
And a series about magic
I'm really worried that I can't shoot well
I hope after everyone appreciate
You acn give me some criticism and advice of the photos
Before the video starts
I want to tell everyone
Because it's material is made by cotton
And
Although I have iron and clean up cat hair
Because I have three cats
It still has some wrinkled feeling or
Not good enough
Please forgive me and hope everyone can be considerate
I'm sorry about that
At the beginning
First of all we have to say
Everyone can take a look at my costume
I'm from HufflePuff College
At the beginning
Because of the movie
Although everyone should be
Gryffindor or Slytherin are more
At first I thought I should be Gryffindor
because
When I was young I felt that Gryffindor was the best
And Slytherin is the worst
But in the end I felt that I should be
Hufflepuff
Because I am not as smart as Ravenclaw
Nor as courageous as Gryffindor
Nor as ambitious as Slytherin
So
I think at least my only strength is kindness
Can I say that?
I don’t think people can be 100% of kind
But I think I should be regarded as a kind-hearted
Witch
Let's take a look at the first set
HufflePuff
The first set of HufflePuff’s signature yellow
I bought this cloak at Universal
I feel it is
Cute
All right
Everyone can look at the bow tie
It's a complete set
And there is this school badge on the chest
There is also a copper badge inside the skirt
And behind it is Hefpaff’s
Sailor collar
This one is blue
Then I think it feels like college
Then because it's Ravenclaw
and so
I make him feel very smart
The feeling of holding a pile of books
I don’t think they made the bow
Very orthodox
But I really like this place around his waist
Everyone can see
Each piece has a different color in each college
do you know?
When the sorting cap was divided into wonderful beauty
It is hesitating to say whether to assign Hermione Jean Granger to Ravenclaw
Because she is so smart
It should be said that it is just a personality trait
Maybe there is a person who actually has 4 talents
4 ability
Maybe he has it
Finally
It’s a very popular Gryffindor
I tied a ponytail
Looks more vitality
Be vigorous
Then please ignore the hem of my dress
I seem to forget to make it swing
And I don’t know where did I put the bow tie
So I matched a tie by myself
But I think it shouldn’t be matched look so bad
Then this scene
I'm learning from Hermione Jean Granger
The scene when she was making the transformation potion before
Although my appearance is not as good as
Hermione Jean Granger
but
when I'm imitate my idol
I still feel pretty happy
Antlers, I wanted to test everyone, which character is called Antlers？
At last
I want to apologize to everyone
Just embarrassed
I don't have Slytherin uniform
Because I said I need to be see things in black and white
The two attitudes stand in sharp contrast
This is my personality
but
When I read the novel a few times after I grow up
Although when I was a child
This is another story
Anyway, when I was young, my family was very strict
Have no computer have no mobile phone
Have no TV or something of technology
So I just read Harry Potter novels all day
Then from episode 1 to that time, how many episodes did it appear? episode 5 ?
Then read from episode 1 to episode 5
Then after reading it
, I will look back from the first episode to episode5 , This is a cycle
Then I would take a flashlight and read Harry Potter inside the bed
Then I felt I just like Harry Potter
hide inside the bedand read the magic book when he during holidays
The same feeling of that
No! I want to apologize to everyone
I don’t have clothes of Slytherin
But after when I growing up
We don ' t live in a world of black and white morality
It's just like
Severus Snape is
Slytherin's
But you think he is a bad guy？
He really is a bad guy？ Does he ？
He is really harmful？Does he？
Did he really kill? Does he？ I think
actually he just
Wants to blend in with everyone
He doesn't have his
Own social circle
So
He will
Want to take refuge
The power of Lord Voldemort
Because he wants to make himself stronger
But I think he is essentially good
And the people in Graffindor are really good? Does them ？
In fact, you see that Luna Lovegood have bullying of other students andLuna Lovegood’s
things will be hidden
And even
Harry Potter's Dad James Potter
At that time, although both parties James Potter andSeverus Snape were fighting and play
tricks on themselves
But this is also an active of bullying
So I feel
Is really like this? So in the end I discovered that the four colleges have their own advantage and disadvantage
It's doesn't
Only the dark wizard is assigned to Slytherin
And because I really took this recently
Then I felt that one Slytherin uniform was missing
I think it's a pity
So
I just search internet about Slytherin unifors
Before I searched, the meow shop
It sold the series of co-branded with Harry Potter again
So
I bought Slytherin's immediately
But it may not be seen in this video
I'm really sorry about that
I hope this video can
???
Can make you happy when you watch this video
I really like Harry Potter very much
If anyone also likes Harry Potter
Wizards！
Want to see me share more about that
I've been to Universal Studios in Japan before
Then I went to New York to see that
The Musical of the Cursed Child
Then I bought some accessories
If you want to see
I hope you can support me
So
see you next time
nox
I recommend a YouTuber called Frog Knife Saint
He did a very detailed analysis of Harry Potter
If you are interested, you can visit his channel